oneyearmba.co.in 2019-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Oneyearmba.co.in

The world's No.1 website for news & guidance on One Year MBA programmes around the world

At Oneyearmba.co.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (See [this article](http://www.wp-insert.smartlogix.co.in/what-is-a-privacy-policy/) to learn more about Privacy Policies.). This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Oneyearmba.co.in and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, Oneyearmba.co.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Oneyearmba.co.in does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Oneyearmba.co.in.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Oneyearmba.co.in and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Oneyearmba.co.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Oneyearmba.co.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Oneyearmba.co.in’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites.

**Data Use**

Our data usage policy (“Policy“) explains how personal information is collected, used and disclosed by OneYearMBA.co.in, (“OneYearMBA.co.in“, “we” or “us“) with respect to your access and use of the OneYearMBA’s website at www.oneyearmba.co.in or any other OneYearMBA tool or service, including those accessible through websites maintained, in whole or in part, by OneYearMBA, or through mobile devices, applications or software (collectively, the “Service“) so you can make an informed decision about using the Service. These include services offered by OneYearMBA such as ONEConnect and services offered by third parties through OneYearMBA.

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on this Policy the date it was last updated and notifying you via the Service. Your privacy is important to us, so we encourage you to review this Policy from time-to-time to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide to us or is collected about you will be used.

**What Is Personal Information?**  
As used in this Policy, the term “personal information” means information that specifically identifies an individual (such a name, user name or e-mail address), or information about that individual that is directly linked to personally identifiable information. Personal information does not include anonymous information, nor does it include “aggregate” information, which is data we collect about the use of the Service or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of anonymous or aggregate information.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
Active Collection: We collect information from you in various ways when you use the Service. For example, we collect information: (i) that you voluntarily provide to us (such as when you send us an email); (ii) that you allow us to access, including information from third parties; and (iii) about you that is publicly available. Such information may include personal information, such as your name, email address, gender, date of birth, city of residence, social network data and performance related data. Personal and demographic information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with posting data, providing access to your online groups and other activities in connection with the Service or in response to a campaign or attendance of an event etc organised by us or third parties using the services of OneYearMBA.

Passive Collection: When you use the Service, some information is also automatically collected, such as your IP address, your operating system, the browser type, mobile phone type, the address of a referring website, and your activity on the Service. We may also automatically collect certain activity information in server logs, including information about how you use various features of the Service and information about the number, frequency and length of each session. We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive at the request of a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve the Service and your experience. If we link cookies to any personally identifying information, we will treat this information as personal information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser manufacturer to learn about these functions. However, if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services made available via the Service. We may use Web beacons or similar technology on the Service. Web beacons are small, invisible graphic images that may be used on the Service or in emails relating to the Service to collect certain information and monitor user activity on the Service, such as to count visits, understand usage effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. We may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. In some situations we store information about accounts connected to OneYearMBA and account credentials in order to provide a more seamless cross-platform experience as you add additional devices through which you’d like to access OneYearMBA.

**How Do We Use the Personal Information We Collect?**  
We use personal information collected through the Service for the purposes described in this Policy or elsewhere on the Service. For example, we may use personal information we collect:

to provide and maintain the Service or information you request, and to process and complete any transactions in connection therewith;  
to request feedback and to otherwise contact you about your use of the Service;  
to respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests and complaints, and to provide customer service;  
to monitor and analyze Service usage and trends;  
to personalize and improve the Service, and our users’ experiences with the Service (such as providing content or features that match interests), and to increase the Service’s functionality and user friendliness;  
to provide you with news and information about our or third party events, offers, promotions and services we think will be of interest to you;  
to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages, and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Service;  
to notify you about important changes to the Service; and for any other purpose for which the information was collected.  
**What Personal Information Do We Share With Third Parties?**  
We may share the personal information we collect from you through the Service with third parties  and by use of the service you give us your consent to do so. For example, we may share personal information as follows:

with vendors, consultants, and other service providers (“Service Providers“) who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Service and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us.

:when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants, or court orders;

:when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of OneYearMBA, our users, our employees, copyright owners, third parties or the public including without limitation to protect OneYearMBA or our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate, or unlawful use of the Service;  
to enforce or apply this Policy, the Terms, or our other policies or agreements; and  
in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where personal information may be disclosed or transferred as one of the business assets of OneYearMBA.

You understand that when you use the Service, provide information via the Service, allow us to access information for the Service, as well as share any information with individuals through the Service, that information may be available to other users and in some cases may be publicly available.

We are not responsible for the actions of Service Providers or other third parties and their use of the demographic or any other user data provided by us, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to any other users or third parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with third party privacy practices before disclosing information directly to any such third parties. Nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregated or anonymized information, which may be shared with third parties without your consent.

**Links to Other Websites**  
The Service may contain links to other websites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. This Policy does not apply to such linked websites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites or any other websites that are linked to/from the Service. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

**What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information Online and Your Data?**  
Again, because your privacy is important to us, we take reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can guarantee against any interception or any other type of misuse. To assist with the protection of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Service by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.

**Data security is also a top priority for OneYearMBA. We use the following third party products with our Services:**

**What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Use of Your Information?**  
If you choose to publicly share information while using the Service, you acknowledge that this information may be accessed, duplicated, reproduced, stored or used by any third party that has access to the public location where you posted your information. You are further acknowledging that OneYearMBA is not responsible for any third party use of your information.

**Use by Persons Under 13**  
OneYearMBA does not intend to direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we become aware or are notified that a user is under age 13, we will take reasonable steps to delete any Personal Information from that user’s account.

Questions?  
If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

(Visited 295 time, 1 visit today)
